Inventory of the Chi Pham Phuoc letters
Hoover Institution Archives
Chi Pham Phuoc letters
1960-1975
2008C12
Hoover Institution Archives
1 manuscript box (0.4 linear feet)
Letters to Mr. and Mrs. Ward Grisham, relating to the Vietnam War. Includes newspaper issues, dress designs, and photographs.
Chi, Pham Phuoc.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2008.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
South Vietnamese soldier.
Scope and Content of Collection
Letters to Mr. and Mrs. Ward Grisham, relating to the Vietnam War. Includes newspaper issues, dress designs, and photographs.
Grisham, Ward.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975.
- Correspondence, 1960 (Text 1: 1)
- Correspondence, 1961 (Text 1: 2)
- Correspondence, 1962 (Text 1: 3)
- Correspondence, 1963 (Text 1: 4)
- Correspondence, 1964 (Text 1: 5)
- Correspondence, 1965 (Text 1: 6)
- Correspondence, 1966 (Text 1: 7)
- Correspondence, 1974 - 1975 (Text 1: 8)
- Correspondence, undated (Text 1: 9)
- Correspondence, Envelopes, undated (Text 1: 10)
- Dress Designs, undated (Text 1: 11)
- News Clippings, 1963 - 1964 (Text 1: 12)
- Photographs, circa 1963 - 1966 (Text 1: 13)
  Scope and Contents note
  Photographs came in an envelope with writings not necessarily pertaining to photographs. Photographs come in different sizes with varying writings on the back. Photographs include a portrait of Chi Pham Phuoc, what appears to be a family portrait, Chi translating documents while in the field, snapshots of Chi in military garb, an image of the prisoner compound, and group photographs.